https://www.santaclaritaautokey.com/legal/

Skip to content
DISCLAIMER - TERMS AND CONDITIONS
BY VISITING THE SANTACLARITAAUTOKEY.COM WEBSITE (THE "SITE" OR "WEBSITE") OR BY OTHERWISE INTERACTING WITH THE SITE, YOU ("CLIENT") AGREE TO ACCEPT THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THE FOLLOWING DISCLAIMER NOTICE:
USE OF WEBSITE
Under no circumstances will Compu-Eze Inc. ("CEI") be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive or consequential damages that may result in any way from your use, misuse, reference to or reliance on any of the information provided on or through this Website or any other web site including those sites which are linked herein, or that result from mistakes, errors, omissions, interruptions, defects, or any failure of performance. CEI may choose to change the terms, conditions, prices quoted within and operation of this Site at anytime without prior notice. By using the Site the user waives any rights or claims it may have against CEI. CEI expressly disclaims all warranties, including any express or implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose with respect to the information herein. While CEI makes every effort to present accurate and reliable information on this Site, CEI does not endorse, approve or certify the information provided by others, nor does CEI guarantee its accuracy, completeness or timeliness. Use of the information directly provided in this Site or others is voluntary and reliance on it should only be undertaken after you have independently verified its accuracy, completeness and timeliness.
COMPUTER HARDWARE WARRANTY:
Any and all computer systems and/or parts purchased from CEI are covered under the existing original manufacturer's warranties. Client may return any part or computer system within 10 working days of original purchase date ONLY IF all original packing materials are present and part or computer system is in resalable condition. Should the part or computer system require warranty service due to malfunction or defect, the client MUST contact the manufacturer directly for warranty service UNLESS client has purchased an extended warranty plan from CEI,
This warranty does NOT apply to persons who purchase this product second-hand or used nor does it apply to repairs required by but not limited to fire, accident, neglect, abuse or misuse. CEI shall not be liable for any consequential, incidental, or punitive damages resulting from any failure, malfunction or injury due to the use of this product. Client waives the right to sue or seek legal action against CEI and in no event shall CEI be liable for any losses or damages beyond the purchase price of the computer, component, and/or originally installed software. Some states do not allow exclusions or limitations on warranties or liabilities, so the above limitations may not apply to you. This warranty gives you specific legal rights, which may vary from state to state.
PLEASE NOTE: CLIENT IS ADVISED TO BACK UP ALL PERSONAL DATA OFTEN, SINCE WARRANTY WORK WILL ONLY COVER REPLACEMENT AND/OR RESTORATION OF ORIGINALLY INSTALLED HARDWARE AND/OR SOFTWARE, AND CEI WILL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR LOSS OR RECOVERY OF PERSONAL DATA. Attempts by the client to fix the computer by opening the cover or allowing unqualified personnel to tamper with ALL and ANY internal components may automatically and permanently VOID existing warranties. CEI tech support must always be called BEFORE any attempts to modify original hardware/software configurations are made to avoid warranty voidance. Any damages, or any other problems arising from the addition or modification to the original PC configuration, including upgrades, will NOT be covered under warranty. ALL software, whether OEM or after-market, and ANY problems arising from such software, including when pertaining to originally installed hardware, are NOT covered under warranty - ANY AND ALL PROBLEMS ARISING FROM SPYWARE AND/OR VIRUSES ARE NOT COVERED UNDER WARRANTY - ALL issues pertaining to software-related problems must be directed to the software's manufacturer. THE ABOVE WARRANTY IS THE ONLY WARRANTY MADE BY CEI. CEI DOES NOT MAKE AND SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY OTHER WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. ALL WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE EXPRESSLY EXCLUDED.
AUTOMOTIVE KEYS
CEI facilitates the provision and programming of generic and/or  OEM automotive transponder keys and fobs to the consumer for pre-determined rates of parts, cutting  and programming fees. Fees may vary according to vehicle,market rates for parts and difficulty of programming sequence. By signing a work order the Client gives CEI permission to connect to Client's vehicle through the OBD port and perform programming functions related to the vehicle transponder system. It may be necessary to access glove box, center console, or other parts of the interior during programming of keys/fobs. Although every effort is made to complete the programming and cutting phases in a short period of time, it may be necessary at times to allow CEI longer periods of time to successfully complete programming due to unforseen circumstances which may arise. If programming is not successful, Client will not be charged for services unless otherwise agreed to in advance. Keys requiring laser cuts will be charged at a higher rate.
GENERAL LIABILITY:
CEI IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES TO YOU OR YOUR BUSINESS AS A RESULT OF CEI'S ACTION OR FAILURE TO ACT. CEI MAKES NO WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO THE SERVICES CEI PROVIDES. CEI DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTY OR MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OF ANY OF SUCH SERVICES. THIS INCLUDES LOSS OF DATA RESULTING FROM DELAYS, NON-DELIVERIES, WRONG DELIVERY, AND ANY AND ALL SERVICE INTERRUPTIONS YOU MAY SUFFER WHETHER OR NOT CAUSED BY CEI OR ITS EMPLOYEES OR VENDORS. IN NO EVENT SHALL CEI BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, INCLUDING LOSS OF PROFIT OR GOODWILL, FOR ANY MATTER, WHETHER SUCH LIABILITY IS ASSERTED ON THE BASIS OF CONTRACT, TORT, OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF CEI HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOU AGREE THAT CEI'S TOTAL LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE TOTAL FEES PAID BY YOU TO CEI PRIOR TO ANY ACT OR OMISSION GIVING RISE TO SUCH DAMAGES. CEI RESERVES THE RIGHT TO REFUSE SERVICE.
Privacy NoticeThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for santaclaritaautokey.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (661) 476-0579 or via email at info@santaclaritaautokey.com.
Copyright © Compu-Eze Inc.
